Friends.
友人だ｡
I am absolutely exhausted.
本当に疲れ果てている｡
I am exhausted and a little tiny bit traumatized.
疲れきっているし､ ちょっとだけトラウマになっている｡
And you are somewhat to blame for this, as you will discover.
そして､ その責任はあなたにもある｡
You will discover in a moment you will find out why.
その理由はすぐにわかるだろう｡
But first, let's talk about what we have in store for today.
その前に､ 今日の予定について話そう｡
So we are going to be raising the bar on our baselines.
だから､ ベースラインのハードルを上げていくつもりだ｡
I'm just going to take a moment to remind you what you can already do.
すでにできることを思い出してほしい｡
Of course, generating text and generating code from combinations of frontier models with AI assistants,
もちろん､ AIアシスタントを使ったフロンティアモデルの組み合わせからテキストを生成したり､ ツールを使ってコードを生成したり､
with tools, and also open source systems using hugging face Transformers library, you can use Lang
抱き合わせ顔変換ライブラリを使ったオープンソースシステムもあり､ ラングチェーンを使ってラグパイプラインを構築することもできるし､
chain to build a rag pipeline, and now you can also curate data and you can curate it.
今ではデータをキュレーションすることもできる｡
Finally, if I may say so.
最後に､ 言わせてもらえば｡
And you can also make a baseline model using some rather foolish techniques.
また､ かなり馬鹿げたテクニックを使ってベースラインモデルを作ることもできる｡
But then using traditional machine learning linear regression, including both feature engineering and
しかし､ 特徴工学とバッグ・オブ・ワードの両方を含む伝統的な機械学習の線形回帰を使い､
bag of words, and then onto more sophisticated techniques using word two vec and then adding in support
さらにワード2ベクトルを使ったより高度な技術を使い､ サポートベクターマシン､ そしてランダムフォレストを加える｡
Quite a trek it's been.
かなりの旅だった｡
So today.
だから今日も｡
Today we are going to now take the framework we put together and put it against frontier models.
今日は､ 私たちが組み立てたフレームワークを､ フロンティア・モデルに当てはめてみよう｡
And this will sort of really capture all of the steps it takes to take a proper business problem, um,
そしてこれは､ 適切なビジネス上の問題を取り上げ､ データを理解し､ それをフロンティア・モデルに提示し､
understand the data and then present it to frontier models and compare their performance.
そのパフォーマンスを比較するために必要なすべてのステップを実際に捉えることになる｡
So it's an exciting moment for us, and we will get right to it.
だから､ 我々にとってはエキサイティングな瞬間だ｡
And I will see you over at JupyterLab in a moment.
それではまたJupyterLabでお会いしましょう｡